I Will Survive
At first
I was afraid
I was petrified
Kept thinking
I could never live without you by my side
But then
I spent so many nights thinking how you did me wrong
And I grew strong
And I learned how to get along
And so you're back from outer space
I just walked in to find you here with that sad look upon your face
I should have changed that stupid lock
I should have made you leave your key
If I had known for just one second you'd be back to bother me
Go on now go walk out the door
Just turn around now 'cos you're not welcome anymore
Weren't you the one who tried to hurt me with goodbye?
Did you think
I'd crumble?
I'd lay down and die?
Oh no not
I, I will survive
Oh as long as
I know how to love
I know
I'll stay alive
I've got all my life to live and
I've got all my love to give
And I'll survive
I will survive, hey hey
It took all the strength
I had not to fall apart
Kept trying hard to mend the pieces of my broken heart
And I spent oh so many nights just feeling sorry for myself
I used to cry but now
I hold my head up high
And you see me somebody new
I'm not that chained up little person still in love with you
And so you felt like dropping in and just expect me to be free
Well now
I'm saving all my lovin' for someone who's loving me
Go on now go walk out the door
Just turn around now 'cos you're not welcome anymore
Weren't you the one who tried to break me with goodbye?
Did you think
I'd crumble?
I'd lay down and die?
Did you think
Oh no, not
I, I will survive
Oh as long as
I know how to love
I know
I'll stay alive
I've got all my life to live and
I've got all my love to give
And I'll survive
I will survive, oh
Go on now go walk out the door
Just turn around now 'cos you're not welcome anymore
Weren't you the one who tried to break me with goodbye
Did you think
I'd crumble?
I'd lay down and die?
Oh no not
I, I will survive
Oh as long as
I know how to love
I know
I'll stay alive
I've got all my life to live and
I've got all my love to give
And I'll survive
I will survive,
I will survive
Oh as long as
I know how to love
I know
I'll stay alive
I've got all my life to live and
I've got all my love to give
And I'll survive
I will survive, hey hey